W. R. "Bob" Poage Personal papers, Inclusive: 1766-2008, undated, Bulk: 1937-1978
Baylor University Libraries
- Travel, 1930-1979, undated; 5
  - Poage Trips, 1944-1979, undated; 1
    - Travel Reimbursement Vouchers, 1973 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Travel Reimbursement Vouchers, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Travel Reimbursement Vouchers, 1975 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Travel Reimbursement Vouchers, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Travel Reimbursement Vouchers, 1978 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - “Travelling with Congressman Jones”, 1959 October (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Tunisia, Conference Reports and Itinerary, 1964 November (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Tunisia, Embassy Brief, 1963 March 5 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - United Kingdom, General Booklets, circa 1944 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Upper Volta, Itinerary, 1970 November 6-7 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Upper Volta, Map and Memorandum on Agriculture committee Trip, 1970 November (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Venezuela, Memorandum, Map, and Schedule, 1973 June-August (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Venezuela, Report on Proposed Financing Projects, 1973 August (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Venezuela, Travel Itinerary, undated (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Venezuela, Travel Journal, 1973 August (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Vienna, Austria, International Atomic Energy Agency Booklets, 1969 March (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Vienna, Austria, Interparliamentary Union Correspondence, 1954 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Vienna, Austria, Itineraries and Schedules, 1969 April (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Vienna, Austria, Memorandums, Schedules for Interparliamentary Union Trip, 1969 March (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Vienna, Austria, Travel Journal, 1969 April (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Vietnam, Itinerary, 1966 December (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Warsaw, Poland, India, East Asia, and Australia, Itineraries and Programs, 1959 September (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Warsaw, Poland, India, East Asia, and Australia, Travel Journal, 1959 August-October (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Warsaw, Poland, India, East Asia, and Australia, Trip Correspondence, 1959 April-December (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Warsaw, Poland, India, East Asia, and Australia, Trip Expenses, 1959 September (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Warsaw, Poland, Interparliamentary Union, Correspondence, 1959 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Warsaw, Poland, Interparliamentary Union, Reports and Minutes, 1959 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Warsaw, Poland, Interparliamentary Speeches, 1959 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Washington, D.C., Interparliamentary Union Correspondence, 1953 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Wongan Hills, Australia, Field Day Briefs, 1956 October (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Yugoslavia, Travel Journal, 1963 September (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Travel Information, 1930-1978, undated; 2
    This subseries consists of items collected during Representative Poage’s professional and personal travels. Maps, brochures, booklets, and postcards from all over the world can be found throughout this subseries. Languages depicted in this subseries include English, French, German, Japanese, Korean, Portuguese, and Spanish. There is an assortment of oversized maps, books, and other documents. Only a few items in the subseries are acidic or otherwise fragile, with everything else in good condition. Folders are listed in alphabetical order and are generally grouped by geographical region.
    Geographical Region names are maintained as Poage would have experienced or mentioned them. Some places that he visited have become new countries or presently use different names.
    America: United States
    Belgian Congo: Democratic Republic of Congo
    French Equatorial Africa: Central African Republic, Chad, Democratic Republic of Congo, Gabon
    Korea: South Korea
    Rhodesia: Zambia, Zimbabwe
    Swaziland: Eswatini
    Upper Volta: Burkina Faso
    USSR: Russia, Georgia, Ukraine, Moldova, Belarus, Armenia, Azerbaijan, Kazakhstan, Uzbekistan, Turkmenistan, Kyrgyzstan, Tajikistan
    Yugoslavia: Serbia, Montenegro
    - Africa, “Presence of France in Africa”, 1957 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Algeria, Postcards, undated (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - America, Conoco Road Maps, undated (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - America, Gulf Oil Road Maps, undated (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - America, Periodical, Agriculture, undated (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - America, Postcards, undated (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - America, Regional Maps, circa 1970 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - America, Road Maps, 1937-1971 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - America, “Scenicland U.S.A.,” Booklet on Western America, 1965 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - America, Standard Oil Road Maps, 1933 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - America, State and National Park Maps, 1947-1977 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - America, Visit of French President Georges Pompidou to the United States, Informational Packet, 1970 February-March (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Amtrak and Greyhound Timetables, 1973-1976 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Antarctica, Informational Packet, 1964 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Argentina, Travel and Embassy Booklets for Frances Poage, circa 1962 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Arizona, Road Maps, 1965-1977 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Australia, Handbook, 1954 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Australia, Infographics on Sugar, circa 1970 (Box 127 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Australia, Land Development Booklets, 1948-1956 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Australia, Postcards, undated (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Australia, Road Maps, 1956 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Australia, Souvenir Book and Posters, 1973 (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Bangladesh, “Bangladesh Observer”, 1972 November 25 (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - Bangladesh, Newspaper Clippings, 1972 November (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Bangladesh, Speeches and Booklets, 1972 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Bangladesh, Travel Booklets, 1972 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Barbados, Postcards, undated (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Bavarian Germany, Picture Book, 1946 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Belgian Congo, Industrial Publication, circa 1955 (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Belgian Congo, Postcards, undated (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Belgian Congo, Travel Brochures, undated (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Bell County, Texas, Road Map, 1970 (Box 127 OVZ, Folder 13)
    - Belton, Texas, Brochure and Map, 1964 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Beograd, Yugoslavia, Brochures, 1969 April (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Beograd, Yugoslavia, Postcards, undated (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - Bethlehem, Jordan, Postcards, undated (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Braniff Airways, Timetables, 1958-1978 (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Brazil, Brochures and Maps, 1972 (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - Brazil, Magazine, circa 1970 (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - Brazil, “Ports & Navigation”, 1939 (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Brazil, Postcards, undated (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - Brazil, “Rodovia,” Magazine, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Brazil, Tourism Booklet, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Brazil, Varig Airlines Flight Booklet, undated (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Brazil, Varig Airlines In-Flight Menu, 1973 (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - Brazil, World Energy Conference Publication, 1970 May (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - British Honduras, Postcards, undated (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Brussels, Belgium, Brochures and Maps, 1976 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Brussels, Belgium, Postcards, undated (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Brussels, Belgium, Tourism Booklet, 1958 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Budapest, Hungary, Brochures, 1969 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Cairo, Egypt, Agriculture Booklets, 1965 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Cairo, Egypt, Travel Brochures, 1965 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - California, Agricultural Booklets, circa 1971 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Canada, Booklets and Brochures, 1965 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Canada, Road Maps, 1965 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Canada, Senate Booklets, 1960 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Canary Islands, Postcards, undated (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Cape Town, South Africa, Travel Brochures, circa 1957 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Central African Republic, Postcards, undated (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Chad, Postcards, undated (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Ciudad Trujillo, Dominican Republic, Speeches, 1955 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Cleveland, Ohio, Great Lakes Exposition Pamphlet, undated (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Colorado, Postcards, undated (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Colorado Springs, Colorado, Travel Guide, 1960 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Congo, Brazzaville, Elizabethville, Stanleyville, Brochures, circa 1954 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Continental Airlines Timetables, 1975-1977 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Copenhagen, Denmark, Brochures and Maps, 1964 (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Copenhagen, Denmark, Postcards, undated (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - Cotton Producer’s Association, Booklet, 1967 (Box 111, Folder 15)
    - Costa Rica, Postcards, undated (Box 111, Folder 16)
    - Dakar, Senegal, Agriculture Magazine, 1957 (Box 111, Folder 17)
    - Dakar, Senegal, Brochures and Maps, 1957 (Box 111, Folder 18)
    - Dakar, Senegal, Economic Brief, 1958 August (Box 111, Folder 19)
    - Dakar, Senegal, Field Guide, circa 1958 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Delta Airlines Timetables, 1972-1975 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Dominican Republic, Guide for Committee on Agriculture, 1955 March (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Dubrovnik, Yugoslavia, Postcards, undated (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - East Pakistan, Brochure, undated (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Eastern Airlines Timetables, 1975-1979 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Ecuador, Postcards, undated (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Ethiopia, Postcards, undated (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Flight Schedules and Tickets, 1963 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Falls County, Texas, Survey Map, 1974 (Box 127 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - Fort Hood, Texas, Hunting Map, circa 1962 (Box 127 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - France, Chamber of Agriculture Pamphlets, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - France, Hennessy Cognac Postcards, undated (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - French Equatorial Africa, Book and Map, circa 1957 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - French Equatorial Africa, Brochure, circa 1956 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - French Western Africa, “A.O.F. Magazine”, circa 1955 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - French Western Africa, Brochures, 1955-1957 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - French Western Africa, Industrial and Agricultural Edition of “A.O.F. Magazine”, 1957 September (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - French Western Africa, Tourism Encyclopedia, undated (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Frontier and American Airlines Timetables, 1969-1976 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - General Airline Timetables (1 of 2), 1937-1977 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - General Airline Timetables (2 of 2), 1937-1977 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Granada, Postcards, undated (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Greece, Brochures, 1962 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Guatemala, Brochures, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Guatemala, Folder of Maps and Packets, 1970-1973 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Guatemala, Postcards, undated (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Guatemala, Tour Itinerary and Map, 1946 November (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Gulf of Mexico, Map [FRAGILE], 1934 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Hawaii, Interparliamentary Union Pamphlets, 1966 April (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Hawaii, Road Maps, circa 1966-1978 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - India, Economic Trends and Conditions, Booklets, 1966 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - India, Political Map [FRAGILE], 1964 November (Box 127 OVZ, Folder 14)
    - India, Postcards, undated (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - India, Travel Brochures, 1959 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Istanbul, Turkey, Postcards, undated (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Italy, Country Overview, 1977 January-February (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Ivory Coast, Postcard, undated (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Japan, Booklets and Maps, undated (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Japan, Postcards, undated (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - Korea, Booklets on State of the Country, 1968-1969 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Korea, Briefing Book, 1968 September (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Korea, Newspaper, “The Korea Herald”, 1969 March 6 (Box 127 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - Korea, Economic Survey Book, 1968 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Korea, Pamphlets and Briefs, 1969 March (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - Korea, Souvenir Calendar, 1969 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Korea, Souvenir Calendar, 1974 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Korea, Souvenir Calendar, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Korea, Travel Brochures, 1968-1969 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Kuwait, Postcard, undated (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Liberia, Postcards, undated (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Madagascar, Postcards, undated (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Madras, India, Newspaper, “American Reporter”, 1959 September (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 8)
    - Madrid, Spain, Brochures, 1957 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Manurewa, New Zealand, East Tamaki Co-Operative Dairy Co. Ltd. Balance Sheet, 1956 May 31 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Massey Agricultural College Booklets, 1957 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Mauritius, Newspaper Clippings, 1970 November 7-11 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Melbourne, Australia, Timetables, 1954 September-November (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Mexico, “Mañana Magazine”, 1962 February 10 (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 9)
    - Mexico, Pamphlet and Map, undated (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Mexico City, Mexico, Travel Booklets and Magazines, circa 1962 (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - Monte Carlo, Monaco, Postcards, undated (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - Montreal, Canada, Canada Expo `67 Materials, 1965 January (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - Montreal, Canada, Expo Journal, 1965 July-August (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 10)
    - Morocco, Postcards, undated (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - Mozambique, Postcards, undated (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - “Murray McDougall and the Story of Triangle,” Book, 1977 (Box 116, Folder 15)
    - Nairobi, Kenya, Postcards, undated (Box 116, Folder 16)
    - New Jersey, Agricultural Booklets, 1965-1967 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - New York World’s Fair, Invitations, 1939 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - New Zealand, Postcards, undated (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Nice, France, Postcards, undated (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Oman, Postcards, undated (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Ontario, Canada, Informational Book, 1967 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Ottawa, Canada, Postcards, undated (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Ottawa, Canada, Travel Brochures, undated (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Paris, France, Book on Le Palais Bourbon, circa 1976 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Paris, France, Decorative Map, undated (Box 127 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Perth, Australia, Maps and Guides, 1955 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Peru, Booklets, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Poland, Brochures, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Poland, Magazine, circa 1972 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - “Planta Productora de Moscas Para control Biologico en Tuxtla Gutierrez,” Brochure, 1976 February (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Port Elizabeth, South Africa, Road Map, undated (Box 127 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - Port of Elizabeth, South Africa, Informational Book, circa 1957 November (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - Portugal, Postcards, undated (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - Prague, Czechoslovakia, Brochures, 1969 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Prague, Czechoslovakia, Welcome Book, 1969 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Queensland, Australia, Map, circa 1972 (Box 127 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - Queensland, Australia, Reports, 1969 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Queensland, Australia, Road Map, undated (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Republic of Niger, Postcards, undated (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Rhodesia, Industrial Publication, 1971 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Rhodesia, Postcards, undated (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Rio Airways and Texas International Airlines Timetables, 1972-1978 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, Booklets on Interparliamentary Union, 1958 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, Brochures, 1972 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, Interparliamentary Union, Flags, 1958 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, Magazine, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, Postcards, undated (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Rockdale, Texas, Brochure, undated (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Salado, Texas, Pamphlet, 1972 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Senegal, Postcards, undated (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Singapore, Postcards, undated (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Sioux City, Iowa, Booklet and Dinner Guest List, 1975 April 30 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Sioux City, Iowa, Map, 1975 (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 12)
    - Somalia, Postcards, undated (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - South Africa Agriculture Reference Maps, undated (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - South Africa Foundation Booklet, 1983 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - South Africa, Map by U.S. Department of Agriculture, undated (Box 127 OVZ, Folder 8)
    - South Africa, Postcards, undated (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - South Africa, “South African Panorama,” Newspaper, 1957 June (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 13)
    - South African Airways, Timetables, 1958 July 1 (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Soviet Union, Map, 1976 (Box 127 OVZ, Folder 9)
    - Soviet Union, Receipts, 1959 (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - Spain, Brochures, 1966 (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - Spain, Newspaper, “Majorca Daily Bulletin”, 1967 March 29 (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 14)
    - Spain, Postcards, undated (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - St. Lambert, Canada, Program for St. Lawrence Seaway, 1969 June 26 (Box 119, Folder 15)
    - Stickers, undated (Box 119, Folder 16)
    - Stockholm, Sweden, Brochures, circa 1964-1965 (Box 119, Folder 17)
    - Stockholm, Sweden, Map on Folder, undated (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 15)
    - Suriname, Postcards, undated (Box 119, Folder 18)
    - Swaziland, “The Times of Swaziland”, 1970 September 4 (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 16)
    - Sydney, Australia, Auction Listing, 1956 December 10 (Box 119, Folder 19)
    - Taiwan, Postcards, undated (Box 119, Folder 20)
    - Taormina, Italy, Postcards, undated (Box 119, Folder 21)
    - Texas, Baylor Geological Study Magazine in Bosque County, 1963 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Texas, Booklet of Maps by Humble Oil, 1930 (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 17)
    - Texas, County Road Maps, 1962-1966 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Texas, HemisFair, Grand Teton, Folders, 1967-1968 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Texas, Humorous Map of Texas, undated (Box 127 OVZ, Folder 10)
    - Texas, Pamphlets on Parks, undated (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Texas, Postcards, undated (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Texas, Randolph Air Force Base, Visit Brief, 1966 May (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Texas, Road Maps (1 of 2), 1931-1975 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Texas, Road Maps (2 of 2), 1931-1975 (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Texas, Secretary of Agriculture’s Listening Conference, Agriculture Booklets, 1969 September (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Texas, Secretary of Agriculture’s Listening Conference, Program, Informational Documents, Speaker List, 1969 September (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - “Texas Today” Magazine, 1969 January (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - Texas, Topographic Map, 1956 August (Box 120, Folder 12)
    - Thailand, Booklets, circa 1956 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Tunis, Postcards, undated (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Tunisia, “Al-Amal” Arabic Newspaper, 1964 November 19 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Uganda, Postcards, undated (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - United Airlines, Baltimore Washington International Timetables, 1972-1978 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Unused Envelopes and Stationery, undated (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Upper Volta, Postcards, undated (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - U.S.S.R., Postcards, Undated (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Utah, Booklets and Postcards, 1968 August (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Utah, Road Maps, 1973-1978 (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Vaduz, Lichtenstein, Postcards, undated (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - Venezuela, Agricultural and Guyana Reports and Booklet, 1972-1973 (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Venezuela, Brochures and Maps, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 13)
    - Venezuela, Brochures of Guyana Region, 1971 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Venezuela, Informational Booklets Prepared by Venezuela Embassy in Washington, D.C., 1973 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Venezuela, Newspaper Clippings, 1973 August (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Venezuela, Newspaper Excerpt from “The Daily Journal”, 1973 August 8 (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 18)
    - Venezuela, Postcards, undated (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Vienna, Austria, Informational Packet, undated (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Vienna, Austria, Shopping Guide, 1967 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Vienna, Austria, Travel Brochures and Maps, circa 1969 March (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Virginia, Holly Farms Visit, circa 1967 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Waco, Texas, Dedication of Lee Lockwood Texas Scottish Rite Library and Museum, 1969 September (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Waco, Texas, Election Results, Newspaper Clippings, 1966 November 10 (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 19)
    - Waco, Texas, Map, undated (Box 127 OVZ, Folder 11)
    - Waco, Texas, Newspaper Clippings, 1966 November 6 (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 20)
    - “Yank The Army Weekly”, 1944 September 22 (Box 127 OVZ, Folder 12)
    - Yemen, Postcards, undated (Box 122, Folder 10)
- Three-Dimensional Artifacts, 1949-1982, undated; 6
  The items in this series are three-dimensional or oddly shaped items collected during Bob Poage's lifetime. A significant portion of this series consists of plaques awarded to the former Representative from a variety of organizations. The series also contains a small button collection, Congressional license plates, presidential pens, flags, Stetson hats, and more.
  This series is primarily in good condition. It is organized alphabetically by item type and description. Most of the items in this series are kept in oversized boxes; however, several items are too large to fit in containers and are kept on the shelves with the collection.
  - Blanket with Baylor University “Sailor Bear” Logo, undated (Box 168 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Book, China, Blue, undated (Box 167 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Book, China, Dark Gray, undated (Box 167 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Book, China, Light Gray, undated (Box 167 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Box, Decorative Box with Mother of Pearl Inlay, circa 1969 August (Box 166 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Briefcase, Brown Leather, undated (Box OVZ)
  - Buttons, Button Sheet #1, 20 Buttons, undated (Box 165 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Buttons, Button Sheet #2, 29 Buttons, undated (Box 165 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Buttons, Button Sheet #3, 10 Buttons, undated (Box 165 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Coin, U.S. Bicentennial and Telephone Centennial, General Telephone Company of the Southwest, 1976 (Box 165 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Cotton, Packet from American Cotton Growers, Crosbyton, Texas, 1974 July 12 (Box 165 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Display, Major Minerals of Burnet County, Texas, Burnet Chamber of Commerce, undated (Box OVZ)
  - Document Case, Green, undated (Box OVZ)
  - Energy Meter, Texas Electric Cooperatives, 1979 July 31 (Box OVZ)
  - Flag, Baylor University, Orange Bowl Classic, 1952 (Box 167 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Flag, Texas State Flag, undated (Box 169 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Flag, U.S. Flag, Placed in Honor of W. R. Poage at Freedom Circle, Brownwood, Texas, undated (Box 169 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Football, Brownwood High State AAA Champs, undated (Box OVZ)
  - Gavel, Wooden Gavel with Six Flags over Texas, undated (Box 170 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Hat, Stetson One Hundred, Dark Grey, Black Box, undated (Box OVZ)
  - Hat, Stetson One Hundred, Light Grey with “Poage” in Head Band, Grey Box, undated (Box OVZ)
  - Hat, Stetson Twenty-Five, Light Grey, Brown Leather Travel Case, undated (Box OVZ)
  - Leather Satchel, undated (Box OVZ)
  - License Plate, Pair of 1972 U. S. Congress Plates for Texas (Box 170 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - License Plate, Pair of 1977 U. S. Congress Plates for Texas (Box 170 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Medal, Democratic National Convention Delegate Medal, 1960 (Box 170 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Medal, Democratic National Convention Name Plate, 1952 (Box 170 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Medal, Democratic National Convention Name Plate, 1960 (Box 170 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Name Plate, Carved Walnut, undated (Box 174 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Name Plate, Office of W. R. Poage, undated (Box 174 OVZ, Folder 2)